

Bogdan Gabriel Balaci

Bucharest, Romania

+40754212223

<u>⊠bogdanbalaci2016@gmail.com</u>

Sex male | Date of birth 11/05/1979 | Nationality Romanian

JOB APPLIED FOR POSITION PREFERRED JOB STUDIES APPLIED FOR Pursuit of continuous professional growth, recognition of experience, skills, dedication and performance are my main objectives and lifelong learning in a dynamic environment is how I plan to reach my goals.

WORK EXPERIENCE

06.2014 - 11.2018

Assistant Manager

S.C NET CONSULTING AND TRADING S.R.L

- Preparation of the offers and specific tourist packages at the clients' request (calculation rates, special offers);
- Selling of service packages to the clients, according to company's offer;
- Making, picking up and checking reservations and preventing problems appeared;
- Preparation of related documents before and during the sale (invoicing, issuing tax and travel documents);
- Keeping good relationships with travel agencies, hoteliers, partners and collaborators;
- Reporting to manager, implementation of his ad hoc decisions;

06.2011 - 12.2011

Sales Representative

GLS GENERAL LOGISTICS SYSTEMS ROMANIA S.R.L.

- Present, promote and sell the company's products/services using solid arguments to existing and prospective customers;
- Perform cost-benefit and needs analysis of existing/potential customers to meet their needs
- Establish, develop and maintain positive business and customer relationships;

07.2010 - 06.2011

Sales Agent

C.N. POSTA ROMANA S.A.

- Contract management
- · Marketing/sales activities

05.2009 - 07.2010

Sales Consultant

S.C. PAN INTERNATIONAL S.R.L BUCHAREST

- · Contract management
- Identifying and attracting developers for exclusive project promotion
- Designing and implementing marketing and sales strategy

11.2006 - 05.2009

Administrator

S.C. ALEBO TRADING S.R.L

- · Develop sales and activity planning
- Sales policies implementation
- Negotiating and signing of contracts
- Supervising the entire activity of the company
- · Budget dimensioning
- Order management

06.2007 - 06.2008

Sales Agent

TOTAL AQUA DISTRIBUTION S.R.L

- · Signing new customers and maintaining relationships with the existing ones
- · Receiving orders
- · Drafting invoices

02.2000 - 06.2004

Tourism agent

S.C. TUDOR TOURISM S.R.L

- · Hotel and transportation booking
- · Invoice issuing
- · Events planning and organizing
- · Business to business relation management with partner agencies and companies

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

09.2008 - 06.2011

High School

CRONOS - Bucuresti

09.1996 - 06.1999

Professional School Grup Scolar Busteni

PROFESSIONAL AND PERSONAL SKILLS

Computer skills

- Good command of Microsoft Office package (excel, word, outlook, power point)
- Excellent internet browsing and online communication skills
- · Excellent social media tools management
- Performance oriented no matter the task
- Job-related skills
- · Good quality control skills acquired while doing various evaluation visits to the postal offices

Communication skills

- Dynamic person with the desire to meet and exceed the expectations · Good communication skills gained through extensive direct contact with customers in the
- · Good communication skills with business partners, contract negotiation, signing and follow up gained as a business to business representative

Mother tongue(s) Other language(s)

• Romanian - native

tourism industry

· English - fluent

Organisational / managerial skills

- Low and middle management level leadership (coordinating teams up to 10 people)
- · Good time management and attention towards details
- · Good task management, work load evaluation and attention towards meeting the timelines

Other skills

- · Experienced driver with endurance on long routes
- · Good crisis management (inside the department and customer related)
- Basic accounting

Driving licence

B category